Neufeld, Maurice Papers /3007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV. ARTICLES AND BOOKS
  - Sub-Series A. Publications
    - Grievance Committees in Italy - Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Contract between MFN and Cornell Univ. re publication of Labor Unions.
    - Grievance Committees in Italy -Distribution and Sales (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Corres and lists re distribution and sales of Labor Unions.
    - Grievance Committees in Italy - Elections. (Box 56, Folder 14)
      Material, including ballots and campaign posters, related to Italian labor union elections. Includes newspaper clippings.
    - Grievance Committees in Italy History (Box 56, Folder 15)
      MFN notes re the history of unionism, communism, and grievance committees in Italy. newspaper clippings
    - Grievance Committees in Italy - Labor Laws., 1951 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      Copies of Rubinacci Labor Bill (in Italian and English translation), introduced in the Italian Parliament on Dec. 4, 1951.
    - Grievance Committees in Italy - News Releases (Box 56, Folder 17)
      News releases re publication of MFN's book. Includes news clippings
    - Grievance Committees in Italy -Unions (Box 56, Folder 18)
      Notes and material re Italian unions. Includes newspaper clippings
    - Grievance Committees in Italy - Wages (Box 56, Folder 19)
      Newspaper clippings re unemployment in Italy
    - House of Labor - Comments, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      News releases, promotional brochures, announcements, comments, and reviews re The House of Labor, edited by J.B.S. Hardman and MFN (New York: Prentice-Hall, 1951).
    - House of Labor - Corrections, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      Manuscript corrections for 1954 reprinting of House of Labor.
    - House of Labor - Correspondence with J.B.S. Hardman, 1950-1951 (Box 56, Folder 22-25)
      Corres from MFN to Hardman re reaction to The House of Labor [12/20/51], corres from Hardman to Wilbur Eastman of Prentice-Hall re title of book [10/27/50], corres from MFN to Hardman re distribution of royalties [10/27/50], corres from MFN to Hardman re early general observations of manuscript [10/13/49], detailed correspondence re editing and revising of the manuscript
    - House of Labor - Correspondence with Others, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 26-29)
      Corres from Wilbur Eastman to J.B.S. Hardman re cost and title of The House of Labor [10/25/50], suggestions by MFN for marketing of House of Labor [7/10/50], general correspondence re marketing of book, editing, and collection of articles
    - Il Mulino - Comments, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 30)
      Comments (in Italian) re MFN's "Il movimento sindicale italiano: panorama di una crisi" (Il Mulino. no. 66, Apr. 1957), an Italian translation of "The Italian Labor Movement in 1956: The Structure of Crisis" (Annals. 1957).
    - Il Mulino - Distribution, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 31)
      Corres and list re distribution of MFN's 1957 Annals article.
    - Il Mulino - Manuscript, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      Copy of 1957 Annals article, corres re the article, notes and charts by MFN.
    - Il Mulino - Reprints (Box 56, Folder 33)
      Copies of April 1957 edition of Il Mulino and reprints of MFN's article
    - Italian Past (IRRA) - Comments, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 34)
      Corres re MFN's article "The Italian Past and the Future of Impoverished Nations," prepared in 1962 for the meeting of the Industrial Relations Research Association (published in Proceedings. IRRA, May 8-9, 1962).
    - Italian Past (IRRA) - Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Italian Past (IRRA) - Distribution (Box 56, Folder 36)
      Corres and list re distribution of IRRA article
    - Italian Past (IRRA) - Manuscript, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 37)
      Manuscript copies of 1962 IRRA article (with MFN notes).
    - Italian Past (IRRA) - Reprints (Box 56, Folder 38)
      Reprints of IRRA article.
    - Exemplar - Comments, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 39)
      Comments re MFN's "The Inevitability of Political Unionism in Underdeveloped Countries: Italy the Exemplar" (Industrial and Labor Relations Review, vol. 13, no. 3, Apr. 1960), including an abstract of the article.
    - Exemplar - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 40)
      Corres from editor of Industrial and Labor Relations Review to MFN re editing of "Exemplar" article [3/4/60].
    - Exemplar - Distribution. (Box 56, Folder 41)
      Corres re distribution of "Exemplar" article
    - Exemplar - Manuscript. (Box 56, Folder 42)
      Copies and revisions of "Exemplar" manuscript.
    - Exemplar - Reprints (Box 56, Folder 43)
      Reprints of "Exemplar" article.
    - Labor History, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Summary of MFN's findings in researching Italy; School for Awakening Countries (Ithaca: NYSSILR, Cornell Univ., 1961. Reprinted Westport, Conn.: Greenwood Press, 1974), presented to the ILR IRRA on Jan. 13, 1959.
    - Labor History - Comments (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
      Reviews, comments, and corres re Italy, including detailed suggestions by Shepard Clough, M. Gardner Clark, and Philip Taft
    - Labor History - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
      Corres from MFN to Robert Aronson, Asst. Director of Research and Publications, ACWA, re consideration of Italy by the ACWA for the Sidney Hillman Foundation Prize [11/3/61], corres from MFN to Gino Giugni re MFN's appraisal of appointments to the Kennedy Cabinet, [11/23/60], routine correspondence
    - Labor History - Distribution (Box 57, Folder 6)
      Corres re distribution and sales of Italy
    - Labor History - Manuscript and Printing. (Box 57, Folder 7)
      Corres and notes re printing and sales of Italy.
    - Labor History - Mistakes, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      Memo from MFN re errors in 1961 printing of Italy.
    - Labor History - Publicity (Box 57, Folder 9)
      Corres re promotion of book, flyers, news releases. Includes newspaper clippings
    - Liberals, Intellectuals, Unionism -Comments., 1964 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      Corres from John W. Lewis to MFN re MFN's "The Historical Relationship of Liberals and Intellectuals to Organized Labor in the United States" (The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science. Nov. 1963) [2/20/64].
    - Liberals, Intellectuals, Unionism Correspondence., 1963 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      Corres from MFN to Albert Blunt re revisions in "Liberals" article [8/13/63], routine correspondence.
    - Liberals, Intellectuals, Unionism -Distribution (Box 57, Folder 12)
      Corres and lists re distribution of reprints of "Liberals" article
    - Liberals, Intellectuals, Unionism - Manuscript. (Box 57, Folder 13-14)
      Copies of "Liberals" manuscript with MFN revisions, manuscript copy of Philip Taft's "Is There a Crisis in the Labor Movement? No."
    - Liberals, Intellectuals, Unionism -Reprints, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      Copies of Nov. 1963 edition of Annals and of reprints of "Liberals" article.
    - Local 3, IBEW (Day In, Day Out with Local 3, IBEW) - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      Corres from MFN to Russell Alien, Int. Brotherhood of Paper Makers, re generalizations in Day In. Day Out with Local 3, IBEW. A Study of Local Union Government and Administration (Ithaca: NYSSILR, Cornell Univ., 1951) [10/3/51], routine correspondence, and a news release.
    - Local 3, IBEW - Documents, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 17-18)
      Includes a copy of Day In, Day Out, and a collection of administrative and organizational material (cards, pamphlets, booklets) and documents outlining employee benefits and apprenticeship plans for Local 3.
    - Local 3, IBEW - Notes, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      MFN notes for 1951 and 1955 editions of Day In. Day Out.
    - Local 3, IBEW - Comments, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      Comments and notices re 1955 reissue of Day In, Day Out. MFN notes, memo from MFN re his meeting with Harry Van Arsdale, Business Manager of Local 3 [10/4/54].
    - Local 3, IBEW - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Local 3, IBEW - Distribution, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      Corres and lists re distribution of Day In. Day Out.
    - Local 3, IBEW - Documents, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 23-24)
      Booklets, cards, and pamphlets outlining Local 3 administration and organization, apprenticeship programs, and employee benefits. Includes newspaper clippings and a photograph.
    - Local 3, IBEW - News Releases, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      News releases re MFN's 1955 Day In, Day Out. Includes newspaper clippings.
    - Local 3, IBEW - Notes, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 26)
      Memo from MFN re a meeting with Van Arsdale [9/25/54], MFN notes for 1955 Day In, Day Out.
    - Local 3, IBEW - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 27)
      Routine correspondence re proposed 1967 revision of Day In, Day Out.
    - Perkins Tribute - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 28)
      Routine corres re MFN's Tribute to Frances Perkins. May 18, 1965 (Ithaca: NYSSILR, Cornell Univ., 1965).
    - Perkins Tribute - Manuscript (Box 57, Folder 29)
      Drafts of Perkins tribute manuscript.
    - Poor Countries - Agreement, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 30)
      Contract between MFN and Cornell University for the publication of Poor Countries and Authoritarian Rule (Ithaca: NYSSILR, Cornell Univ., 1965) [4/29/64].
    - Poor Countries - Comments (Box 57, Folder 31-32)
      Reviews, notices, comments, and publicity re Poor Countries.
    - Poor Countries - Corrections (Box 57, Folder 33)
      Corrections for Poor Countries manuscript
    - Poor Countries - Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series B. Misc. Writings
    - Poor Countries - Manuscript (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
      MFN's notes for Poor Countries, revised copies of manuscript
    - Poor Countries - Publicity (Box 58, Folder 3)
      Corres re distribution and publicity for Poor Countries, news releases, pamphlets, and circulars. Includes a newspaper clipping.
    - Poor Countries - Quotation (Box 58, Folder 4)
      List of quotes used in Poor Countries.
    - Realms of Thought - Labor History Version., 1969 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      Copies of manuscript of "Realms of Thought and Organized Labor in the Age of Jackson" (Labor History, vol. 10, no. 1, Winter 1969).
    - Realms of Thought - Labor History Version - Distribution (Box 58, Folder 6)
      Corres and lists re distribution of reprints of "Realms of Thought".
    - Realms of Thought - London Version, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 7-9)
      Copies and revisions of "Realms of Thought" manuscript, presented by MFN to the Anglo-American Colloquium of the Society for the Study of Labour History at the University of London, June 22-23, 1968.
    - Rivista di Diritto del Lavaro - Distribution, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      Corres and lists re distribution of MFN's "L'unificazione della Federazione Americana del Lavaro (AFL) con il Congresso delle Organizzazioni Industriali (CIO)" (Rivista di Diritto del Lavaro. Anno IX, Fasc. 1-2, Part III, Jan.-Apr. 1957).
    - Rivista di Diritto del Lavaro -Manuscript. (Box 58, Folder 11)
      Manuscript, with MFN notes and revisions, of "The AFL-CIO: A Study in Marriage," the English version of MFN's Rivista article.
    - Rivista di Diritto del Lavaro -Reprints. (Box 58, Folder 12)
      Reprints of MFN's Rivista article
    - Russia, etc. - Correspondence., 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 13-14)
      Corres from MFN to Mikhail A. Menshikov, Soviet Ambassador to the U.S., re MFN's intentions to travel to the U.S.S.R. to study grievance committees [2/18/60], MFN's plan of study [2/18/60], corres from Thomas Lane, Dept. of Labor, re Lane's recommendation of MFN for a Guggenheim Fellowship to research Eastern Europe [11/10/59], corres from Morris Weisz, Dept. of Labor, to MFN re Guggenheim Fellowship [11/2/59], corres from Janusz K. Zawodny to MFN re advice for studying grievance procedures in the U.S.S.R. [10/19/59], routine correspondence.
    - Russia, etc. - Legislation (Box 58, Folder 15)
      Research material re Russian labor law
    - Russia, etc. - Trade Unions. (Box 58, Folder 16)
      MFN notes re the structure of Russian trade unions. Includes newspaper clippings.
    - Sense of History - Comments., 1961 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      Comments and notices re MFN's "The Sense of History and the Annals of Labor," presented to the 1961 meeting of the IRRA (Proceedings. IRRA, Dec. 28-29, 1961).
    - Sense of History - Correspondence (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Sense of History - Distribution (Box 58, Folder 19)
      Corres and lists re distribution of MFN's "Sense of History".
    - Sense of History - Manuscript. (Box 58, Folder 20)
      Revised drafts of MFN's "Sense of History". Includes a newspaper clipping.
    - Sense of History - Reprints (Box 58, Folder 21)
      Reprints of "The Sense of History and the Annals of Labor".
    - Americans as Bolsheviks, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      12p
    - From the Diary of Maurice F. Neufeld, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 23)
      Mar-64
    - I want to Join A Union But -- w/Nora Piore, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      209 p. October 1934.
    - Progressive Mine Workers, Ill., 1932-1933 (Box 58, Folder 25)
      includes some correspondence, notes, clippings
    - The Structure and Government of the AFL-CIO, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      43 p. mss. August 1955.
- Series V. CLASS MATERIALS
  - Sub-Series A. Class Handouts
    - Abelson, P., "Evolution of Collective Bargaining and Agreement Administration in the Needle Trades." (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - ACLU, "Memorandum to Support the Bill Amending the National Labor Relations Act to Promote Democracy Within Labor Organizations." (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - AFL-CIO Chart (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Barnett, George, "The Dominance of the National Union American Labor Organization." (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Bauder, Russell, "Three Interpretations of the American Trade Union Movement", 1943 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      Social Forces. Dec. 1943.
    - Birdsall, William, "The Administration and Organization of Local 603 of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of Ithaca, New York"; "The Problem of Administrative Structure in the Knights of Labor"; "Structure of the National CIO. " (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Blood, Ross D., "What Happens to Your $1.25?" (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Bradburd, A.W., Bibliography: Government Stabilization of Wages in the Maritime Industry During World War II (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics, "Brief History of the American Labor Movement." (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - "By-Laws and Trade Rules of the Carpenter's District Council of Rochester and Vicinity of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Main 5246, Rochester, New York, 1947." (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Commons, John R., "American Shoemakers, 1648-1895: A Sketch of Industrial Evolution"; "An Idealistic Interpretation of History." (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - "Constitution and By-Laws of the Southern Association of Pulp and Paper Industry Unions (A.F. of L. ) Approved by Convention at Mobile, Ala., April 18th-19th, 1952." (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Courses - ILR (Box 59, Folder 13)
      Discontinued - Reading lists
    - Courses - ILR 200 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      Reading lists
    - Courses - ILR 350 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Courses - ILR 351 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Courses - ILR 430 & 530 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Courses - ILR 430 & 530 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      Bibliography
    - Courses - ILR 430 & 530 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      Charts and student papers
    - Courses - ILR 431 & 531 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Courses - ILR 431 & 532 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Courses - ILR 431 & 533 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Courses - ILR 690 (Box 59, Folder 23)
      Friedland & MFN - Reading List
    - Courses - ILR 690 (Box 59, Folder 24)
      Friedland & MFN - Bibliography
    - Crocchiolo, Andrew, "A Review of C. Wright Mills' The New Men of Power--America's Labor Leaders." (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Dunlop's Theoretical Framework Applied to the Speculations of Other Writers about Industrial Relations Systems (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Eaton, Cyrus, "A Capitalist Looks at Labor." (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - FMCS, "Statement of Arbitration Functions and Facilities." (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - "Selected Bibliographies, Indexes & Guides: An Annotated List", 1972 (Box 59, Folder 29)
      Jan. 1972
    - Frick, Elizabeth A., Compiler, "Annotated Bibliography of Bibliographies, Indexes, Abstract Services and Union Lists of Labor Periodicals, Journals, and Newspapers", 1971 (Box 59, Folder 29)
      Sept. 1971
    - Field, Edward, Part I: The Development and Organization of the Independent Union of Airline Maintenance Men of Ithaca, NY; Part II: The National Mediation Board and the Labor Relations of Carriers by Air. (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Gelberg, Alfred, Local Oranizations--Structure and Function; Structure and Functioning of the ILGWU Local Union (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Hey, Emery, Ithaca Typographical Union No. 379 (Box 59, Folder 32)
      State Feds., City Centrals, etc.
    - Hill, Ellen, ACWA Rochester Joint Board; UMWA (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Kerr, Clark, et. al., Industrialism and Industrial Man - Charts. (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Lafore, Laurence, comp., "Jargon Control Program", 1957 (Box 59, Folder 35)
      Harper's Magazine, Aug. 1957
    - Laslett, John H.M., Labor and the Left (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Neufeld, M.F. (Box 59, Folder 37-41)
      Basic Rules for Analyses of Doctrines; Definitions of Radicalism. Dissent, and Reform; History of Organized Labor in the United States; Survey of Labor Union Publications in the Martin P. Catherwood Library; Instructions for Term Papers (ILR 200C)
    - Perlman, Selig, "The Principle of Collective Bargaining." (Box 59, Folder 42)
    - Saposs, Davis J., "Structure of AFL Unions." (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Seidenberg, Jacob, "Structure of Teamsters." (Box 59, Folder 44)
    - Taft, Philip (Box 59, Folder 45-46)
      "The Constitutional Power of the Chief Officer in American Labor Unions"; "Democracy in Trade Unions"; "Dues and Initiation Fees in Labor Unions"; "Judicial Procedures in Labor Unions"; "Opposition to Union Officers in Elections"; "Status of Members in Unions during Appeal from Penalty"; "Understanding Union Administration."
    - Wickersham, Edward D., UMWA--Structure of the Union. (Box 59, Folder 47)
    - Windmuller, John, Analytical History...GM & UAW. (Box 59, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series B. Student Term Papers
    - Miscellaneous term papers, 1946-1976 (Box 60)
- Series VI. MISCELLANEOUS
  - Sub-Series A. Subject Files
    - American Federation of Labor, 1949-1953 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - American Federation of Labor Bldg. & Construction Trades Dept., 1948 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - AFL-CIO, 1955-1971 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Affiliations & membership, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Workers Union (Box 61, Folder 5)
      no date
    - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - American Labor Attache, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Barbash, Jack (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Bernstein, Meyer, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Broderick, Walter, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Brown, Harvey, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Building and Construction Industry, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Building Industry of NYC, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Colbert, Robert, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Collective Bargaining Process, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Communist Party of Ithaca, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Communist Tactics in American Unions, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Democracy Within Labor Organizations, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Deutscher, Oscar, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Eby, Kermit, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Electrical Industry and Cultural Trust Fund, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Equality of Opportunity, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Esso Standard Oil, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ, 1908 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Feldesman, William, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - General Motors, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Goldberg, Arthur, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Good, Roy (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Harbison, Frederick (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Hartman, John, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Hayes, A. J., 1946 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Hollander, Louis, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Hook, Sidney, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Independent Union of Airline, Maintenance Men of Ithaca, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Industrial Commission of Colorado, 1928 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Institute on Living in the Later Years, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - International Association of Machinists, 1956-1957 (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - International Association of Machinists, 1947-1949 (Box 61, Folder 40)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3, 1958-1969 (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 42)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers', 1948 (Box 61, Folder 43)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers', 1938-1947 (Box 61, Folder 44)
    - International Longshoremen's Assn, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 45)
    - Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 46)
    - Kelly, Matthew, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 47)
    - Labor Management Institute, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 48)
    - McNamara Case, 1911 (Box 61, Folder 49)
    - McNulty, Paul, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous, 1903-1963 (Box 61, Folder 51)
    - Mooney, Tom, 1930-1936 (Box 61, Folder 52)
    - National Council of the Churches of Christ, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 53)
    - National Institute for Labor Education (NICE), 1961 (Box 61, Folder 54)
    - NYC Joint Boards (Box 61, Folder 55)
    - NY York State Dept. of Labor, 1948-1950 (Box 61, Folder 56)
    - O'Connor, Donald (IAM-Ithaca), 1957 (Box 61, Folder 57)
    - Oil Industry, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 58)
    - Perlman, Selig, 1910 (Box 61, Folder 59)
    - Railway Labor Executives Assn, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 60)
    - Rates of Pay, 1947-1950 (Box 61, Folder 61)
    - Read, Harry, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 62)
    - Remington-Rand (Box 61, Folder 63)
    - Rubin, Jay, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 64)
    - Sackman, Morris, 1946-1960 (Box 61, Folder 65)
    - Saposs, David, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 66)
    - Seitz, Peter, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 67)
    - Seminar on Labor, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 68)
    - Standard Oil Employee Assn, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 69)
    - Story of Motion-Time-Analysis, 1934 (Box 61, Folder 70)
    - Summers, Clyde, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 71)
    - Taft, Philip, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 72)
    - Taylor, George W., 1962 (Box 61, Folder 73)
    - Telephone Workers Organizing Committee, 1946-1949 (Box 61, Folder 74)
    - Textile Workers Union of America, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 75)
    - Ulman, Lloyd, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 76)
    - Unification-Transport Workers Union, 1939 (Box 61, Folder 77)
    - United Auto Workers, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 78)
    - United Rubber Workers, 1938-1946 (Box 61, Folder 79)
    - U.S. Dept. of Labor, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 80)
    - United Steelworkers of America, 1948-1965 (Box 61, Folder 81)
    - Whyte, W.F., 1956 (Box 61, Folder 82)
    - Witte, Edwin E., 1953 (Box 61, Folder 83)
    - Wolman, Leo, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series B. National Labor Relations Board Files
    - Thomas Willard Holland Manuscript (1 binder) (Box 62)